WHAT AM I SITTING ON?
TOP OF THE WORLD?
DOCK OF THE BAY?
I'M OUT.
EW, UNDIES, OH!
Rachel:
ALL RIGHT.
WHOSE ARE THEY?
NOT MINE.
WELL, THEY'RE JOEY'S.
THEY GOT TO BE JOEY'S.
YEAH, THEY'RE MINE.
SEE, JOEY'S.
THEY'RE J-J-J-J-JOEY'S.
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
I DON'T KNOW, UH...
I'M JOEY.
YEAH, I'M DISGUSTING.
I TAKE MY UNDERWEAR OFF
IN OTHER PEOPLE'S HOMES.
WELL, GET 'EM OUT OF HERE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YEAH.
TAKE 'EM.
OH, I GOT...
JOEY, YOU CAN TOUCH THEM.
THEY'RE YOUR UNDERWEAR.
CHANDLER, A WORD?
YEAH.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TIRED OF COVERING
FOR YOU TWO.
THIS HAS GOT TO STOP.
UGH!
AND TIGHTY-WHITEYS?
WHAT ARE YOU, EIGHT?
THANK YOU, JOEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WELL, HEY, NO,
YOU'RE NOT WELCOME, OKAY?
LOOK, I HATE THIS.
YOU GUYS KEEP EMBARRASSING ME.
YESTERDAY, RACHEL FOUND
YOUR RAZOR IN OUR BATHROOM.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY
SO I SAID IT WAS MINE
AND... AND...
AND THAT I WAS PLAYING
A WOMAN IN A PLAY.
AND, WELL, ONE THING
LED TO ANOTHER AND...
WOW, AND AROUND THE ANKLES.
YOU KNOW, THAT
IS A TOUGH SPOT.
YEAH, IT WAS.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN,
I CAN'T...
ALL THIS LYING HAS BEEN
HARD ON US, TOO.
OH, YEAH, I BET ALL THE SEX
MAKES IT EASIER.
WELL, YEAH, ACTUALLY.
WE'LL TRY TO BE
MORE CAREFUL, OKAY?
IT'S JUST THAT...
WE DON'T WANT
EVERYONE TO KNOW
BECAUSE THIS IS
GOING REALLY WELL.
AND MAYBE
THE REASON
IT'S GOING REALLY WELL IS...
IS BECAUSE IT'S A SECRET.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS
REALLY WEIRD
BUT WE'RE JUST BOTH
SO BAD AT RELATIONSHIPS.
WE ARE. HELP US.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU DO IT WITH ME ONCE.
JOEY.
DIDN'T THINK SO.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, PHOEBE.
HI, PHEEBS.
WHAT ARE
YOU READING?
WUTHERING HEIGHTS.
I'M TAKING A LITERATURE CLASS
AT THE NEW SCHOOL
AND I HAVE TO FINISH IT
FOR THE FIRST SESSION TOMORROW.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
TAKING A CLASS.
THAT'S SO COOL.
YEAH, WELL, I REALLY LIKED
THAT LAMAZE CLASS I TOOK
YOU KNOW, AND I JUST THOUGHT
THIS TIME
I'D GO FOR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE MORE INTELLECTUAL
WITH A LESS PAINFUL FINAL EXAM.
HONEY, THAT
SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
YEAH.
OH, YOU SHOULD
COME WITH ME.
OH, YEAH, THEN I'LL HAVE SOMEONE
TO SIT WITH.
OKAY.
YAY! OKAY.
BUT ARE YOU GOING
TO HAVE TIME TO READ IT?
I READ THAT
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, THIS IS GOING TO BE
SO MUCH FUN.
OKAY, SHH. I HAVE TO FINISH.
HI.
WHAT'S WRONG, BUDDY?
SOMEONE AT WORK ATE MY SANDWICH.
WELL, WHAT DID
THE POLICE SAY?
MY THANKSGIVING LEFTOVER
SANDWICH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE JUST ATE IT.
ROSS, IT'S JUST
A SANDWICH.
JUST A SANDWICH?
LOOK, I AM 30 YEARS OLD,
OKAY?
I'M GOING BE DIVORCED TWICE,
AND I JUST GOT EVICTED.
THAT SANDWICH WAS THE ONLY
GOOD THING GOING ON IN MY LIFE.
SOMEONE ATE THE ONLY GOOD THING
GOING ON IN MY LIFE.
OKAY, LOOK, I
HAVE ENOUGH STUFF
FOR ONE MORE SANDWICH.
I MEAN, I WAS GOING
TO EAT IT MYSELF, BUT...
MON, TH-THAT WOULD BE
INCREDIBLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BUT I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE ATE IT.
I MEAN, LOOK, I LEFT A NOTE
AND EVERYTHING.
"KNOCK KNOCK.
"WHO'S THERE?
"ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH.
"ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH, WHO?
ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH, PLEASE
DON'T TAKE ME, OKAY?"
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T GO HOME
WEARING YOUR LUNCH.
Phoebe:
OKAY, LOOK
YOU WANT TO HOLD ON
TO YOUR FOOD?
YOU'VE GOT TO SCARE PEOPLE OFF.
I LEARNED THAT LIVING
ON THE STREET.
REALLY?
SO, WHAT WOULD YOU SAY, PHEEBS?
STUFF LIKE, UH, "KEEP YOUR MITTS
OFF MY GRUB"?
SAY, ROSS, WHEN YOU PICTURE
PHOEBE LIVING ON THE STREET
IS SHE SURROUNDED
BY THE ENTIRE CAST OF ANNIE?
OKAY, THIS'LL KEEP THEM
AWAY FROM YOUR STUFF.
OH.
WHOA.
JEEZ.
PHOEBE, YOU ARE A BADASS.
SOMEDAY, I'LL TELL YOU ABOUT
THE TIME I STABBED A COP.
PHOEBE?
WHAT? HE STABBED ME FIRST.
SEE, THE BRONTE SISTERS WERE
REALLY REMARKABLE WOMEN
FOR THEIR TIME.
THEY LIVED IN A
PATRIARCHAL SOCIETY...
SORRY I'M LATE,
BUT I LEFT LATE.
OKAY.
PHEEBS, WHAT IS
THE BOOK ABOUT?
YOU SAID YOU READ IT
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YEAH, BUT I
REMEMBERED
I STARTED IT
BUT THEN THERE WAS
THIS PEP RALLY
AND I WAS ON TOP
OF THE PYRAMID.
ANYWAY, WHAT'S
THIS BOOK ABOUT?
OKAY, IT'S THIS
TRAGIC LOVE STORY
BETWEEN CATHY
AND HEATHCLIFF.
AND IT TAKES PLACE ON
THESE REALLY CREEPY
MOORS IN ENGLAND.
WHICH I THINK REPRESENT
THE WILDNESS
OF HEATHCLIFF'S CHARACTER.
I TOTALLY GET SYMBOLISM.
HOW WOULD YOU CHARACTERIZE
THE THEME OF THIS BOOK?
UH, LET'S SEE...
RACHEL GREEN?
UH, WELL, I WOULD
HAVE TO SAY
THAT IT'S A
TRAGIC LOVE STORY.
WELL, THAT'S SORT
OF A GIVEN, BUT... YES.
ANYONE ELSE?
OH, OH, OH.
SYMBOLISM, AND
THE, UH...
WILDNESS OF THE MOORS
WHICH I THINK IS
MIRRORED IN THE WILDNESS
OF HEATHCLIFF'S CHARACTER.
EXCELLENT.
WHAT RACHEL HAS SHREWDLY
OBSERVED HERE
IS AT THE HEART...
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU STOLE
MY ANSWER.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
PRETTY OBVIOUS.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN READ IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UH, YOU, IN THE BLUE SHIRT.
I THINK THAT YOURS
IS A QUESTION
WITH MANY
POSSIBLE ANSWERS.
WOULD YOU CARE TO VENTURE ONE?
WOULD YOU CARE
TO VENTURE ONE?
ARE YOU JUST REPEATING
WHAT I'M SAYING?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE ON.
OKAY, THEN.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY
THAT YOU HADN'T READ THE BOOK?
BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT HIM
TO THINK
I WAS STUPID.
I MEAN, THAT WAS
REALLY EMBARRASSING
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU.
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
PHOEBE, YOUR NOTE...
AMAZING.
NOT ONLY DID NO ONE
TOUCH MY SANDWICH
BUT PEOPLE AT WORK ARE
ACTUALLY AFRAID OF ME.
A GUY CALLED
ME "MENTAL."
"MENTAL" GELLER. YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
A COOL NICKNAME LIKE THAT.
YEAH, THE BEST YOU GOT
IN HIGH SCHOOL
WAS "WET PANTS GELLER."
IT WAS THE WATER FOUNTAIN,
OKAY?!
ANYWAY...
PEOPLE ARE WRITING REPORTS
FOR ME.
UH, PUSHING BACK DEADLINES
TO FIT MY SCHEDULE.
I'M TELLING YOU,
YOU GET TOUGH WITH PEOPLE
AND YOU CAN GET
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
HEY, TRIBBIANI, GIVE ME
THAT COFFEE, NOW.
THIS WAS REALLY FUN.
I'VE BEEN WONDERING
IF YOU WERE EVER
GOING TO ASK ME OUT.
SO YOU, UH, STILL WONDERING?
NO.
WE JUST WENT OUT.
YOU'RE SMART.
I LIKE THAT.
OH, CANDLES.
WHAT IS THAT,
A BLANKET?
A VIDEO CAMERA?
OH, MY GOD!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING TO VIDEOTAPE US
HAVING SEX ON THE FIRST DATE.
HI.
JOEY, IS WHAT SHE
JUST SAID, UM...
OH, MY GOD.
YOU WERE ACTUALLY
GOING TO...
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
AND WITH CHANDLER
IN THE NEXT ROOM?
WHAT, ARE YOU SICK?
I'M JOEY.
I MEAN, I'M DISGUSTING.
I MAKE LOW-BUDGET ADULT FILMS.
HUH.
YOU GUYS PROMISED
YOU'D BE MORE CAREFUL.
I MEAN, COME ON,
THE GOOD JOEY NAME
IS BEING DRAGGED
THROUGH THE MUD HERE.
WE'RE SO SORRY.
YEAH.
WELL, I'M TELLING
EVERYONE ABOUT YOU.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO EXPLAIN THE UNDERWEAR,
AND THE VIDEO CAMERA
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ME
LOOK LIKE A PIG.
NO, WAIT. THERE'S GOT
TO BE A BETTER EXPLANATION.
YOU... YOU COULD
TELL THEM
THAT YOU HAD TO MAKE
AN ADULT FILM
FOR YOUR...
ADULT FILM CLASS.
YEAH, I LIKE THAT.
BUT, NO, HOW DOES THAT EXPLAIN
WHY RACHEL FOUND MY UNDERWEAR
AT YOUR PLACE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, GET READY TO COME
OUT OF THE NON-GAY CLOSET.
JUST WAIT, PLEASE--
I PROMISE WE'LL
COME UP WITH SOMETHING.
JUST GIVE US
A LITTLE MORE TIME.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, BUT IT BETTER MAKE ME
LOOK REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
OH, AND ANOTHER THING.
THE VIDEO CAMERA?
NICE.
UM, ROSS, MAY I HAVE
A WORD WITH YOU?
OH, OF COURSE, DONALD.
WE'VE BEEN GETTING REPORTS
OF SOME VERY ANGRY BEHAVIOR
ON YOUR PART.
WHAT?
THREATENING LETTERS
REFUSAL TO MEET DEADLINES.
APPARENTLY PEOPLE
NOW CALL YOU "MENTAL."
YEAH.
WE WANT YOU TO SPEAK
TO A PSYCHIATRIST.
OH, NO, YOU
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
UH, THIS IS SO SILLY.
UM, THIS IS ALL JUST
BECAUSE OF A SANDWICH.
A SANDWICH?
YOU SEE, MY...
MY SISTER MAKES THESE
AMAZING TURKEY SANDWICHES.
HER SECRET IS, SHE
PUTS AN EXTRA SLICE
OF GRAVY-SOAKED
BREAD IN THE MIDDLE.
I CALL IT THE "MOIST-MAKER."
ANYWAY, I-I PUT
MY SANDWICH
IN THE FRIDGE
OVER HERE, AND...
( chuckling ):
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I-I-I'M SORRY.
I-I-I BELIEVE I ATE THAT.
YOU ATE MY SANDWICH?
IT WAS A SIMPLE MISTAKE.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
OH, OH, REALLY?
DID YOU CONFUSE IT WITH
YOUR OWN TURKEY SANDWICH
WITH A MOIST-MAKER?
NO, I...
DO YOU PERHAPS
REMEMBER SEEING
A NOTE ON TOP OF IT?
THERE MAY HAVE BEEN A JOKE
OR... LIMERICK OF SOME KIND...
THAT SAID IT
WAS MY SANDWICH.
NOW, NOW, CALM DOWN.
COME LOOK IN MY OFFICE.
SOME OF IT MAY STILL BE
IN THE TRASH.
WHAT?
WELL, IT WAS QUITE LARGE.
I HAD TO THROW
MOST OF IT AWAY.
YOU, YOU, YOU...
YOU THREW MY SANDWICH AWAY?
MY SANDWICH?
( yelling ):
MY SANDWICH?!
HI.
SO, UM WHAT'S
THIS BOOK ABOUT?
YOU DIDN'T READ
THIS ONE EITHER?
WELL, I WAS GOING TO
BUT I ACCIDENTALLY READ
SOMETHING ELSE.
WHAT?
VOGUE.
OKAY, SO TELL ME ABOUT
THIS JANE EYRE WOMAN.
NO, YOU SHOULD HAVE READ
IT YOURSELF.
OH, COME ON, PHOEBE
DON'T BE SUCH
A GOODY-GOODY.
FINE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
SO, JANE EYRE?
FIRST OF ALL,
YOU'D THINK SHE'S A WOMAN
BUT SHE'S NOT.
SHE'S A CYBORG.
A CYBORG?
ISN'T THAT LIKE A ROBOT?
YEAH. THIS BOOK WAS LIGHT YEARS
AHEAD OF ITS TIME.
SORRY, I'M LATE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
SO, WHAT DID EVERYBODY
THINK OF JANE EYRE?
UM, RACHEL AND I WERE
JUST DISCUSSING IT
AND SHE ACTUALLY HAD
SOME VERY INTERESTING INSIGHTS.
WELL, GO AHEAD, RACHEL.
UM, THANK YOU, PHOEBE.
UM, WELL, WHAT
STRUCK ME MOST
WHEN READING
JANE EYRE WAS
UH, HOW THE BOOK WAS
SO AHEAD OF ITS TIME.
IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
FEMINISM, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH, WELL,
FEMINISM, YES.
BUT ALSO, THE ROBOTS.
HEY.
SO, UM, SINCE THAT
VIDEO CAMERA THING
DIDN'T WORK OUT...
UM, I THOUGHT THAT
I WOULD GIVE YOU
JUST A LITTLE PREVIEW.
( gasps )
YOU'RE NAKED
IN THIS PICTURE.
I KNOW.
OH, THAT'S ROSS.
ROSS?
HEY, CHANDLER.
MONICA?
ROSS, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
I SAW A PSYCHIATRIST
AT WORK TODAY.
WHY?
ON ACCOUNT OF MY RAGE.
WHICH, IF I MAY SAY
RIGHT NOW, IS OUT OF CONTROL.
HE GAVE ME A PILL FOR IT.
A PILL?
MM-HMM.
WELL, WHEN
THE PSYCHIATRIST TOLD ME
THAT I HAD TO TAKE
A LEAVE OF ABSENCE
BECAUSE I YELLED AT MY BOSS
I STARTED TO GET
WORKED UP AGAIN.
SO, HE OFFERED ME A TRANQUILIZER
AND I THOUGHT IT
WAS A GOOD IDEA
SO I TOOK IT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THEY'RE MAKING YOU
TAKE TIME OFF WORK?
AND YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD
NOT HAVING A JOB FOR AWHILE
BUT I... I DEFINITELY DON'T CARE
ABOUT MY SANDWICH.
( chuckling )
UH, IT WAS JUST
SO EMBARRASSING
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET ME
GO ON AND ON LIKE THAT.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS JUST SO FUNNY
WHEN YOU STARTED COMPARING
JANE EYRE TO ROBOCOP.
THAT WAS NOT FUNNY.
WELL, I SNAPPED, OKAY?
YOU WEREN'T TAKING
THE CLASS SERIOUSLY.
PHOEBE, COME ON,
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS GOING TO BE
SOMETHING WE COULD DO TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUN.
WELL, YEAH, FUN IS GOOD
BUT, YOU KNOW, I ALSO
WANTED TO LEARN.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS
TALKING ABOUT WHAT THEY LEARNED
IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND I NEVER WENT
TO HIGH SCHOOL.
OH.
OH, SO YOU REALLY
WANTED TO LEARN?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, PHEEBS,
I JUST WANTED TO HAVE FUN.
YOU KNOW WHO YOU
SHOULD GO WITH?
I KNOW! I KNOW! I KNOW!
MONICA, YOU ASKED
THE QUESTION.
OH, YEAH.
( gasps )
AH, OH MY GOD!
THAT'S MONICA!
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU GET AWAY FROM ME,
YOU SICK, SICK, SICKO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JOEY HAS GOT
A SECRET PEEPHOLE.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YES. HE HAS A NAKED
PICTURE OF MONICA.
HE TAKES NAKED
PICTURES OF US.
THEN HE EATS CHICKEN
AND THEN HE LOOKS AT THEM.
LOOK.
DUDE, THAT'S MY SISTER.
GIVE ME THAT.
ALL RIGHT, WAIT,
JUST WAIT.
EVERYBODY JUST
CALM DOWN, OKAY?
LET'S GIVE OUR FRIEND JOEY
A CHANCE TO EXPLAIN
WHY HE'S SUCH
A BIG PERVERT.
NO, I AM NOT A PERVERT, OKAY?
IT'S JUST, I JUST KIND OF...
OH LOOK, LOOK,
I THINK I CAN EXPLAIN THIS.
THANK YOU.
JOEY'S A SEX ADDICT.
WHAT?! NO, I'M NOT.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S GOOD.
IT'S A DISEASE.
NO, NO, I AM NOT
A SEX ADDICT.
YES, YOU ARE.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO EXPLAIN
ALL THIS STUFF.
NO, IT ISN'T.
NO, IT'S NOT.
BECAUSE YOU COULD ALSO
EXPLAIN IT WITH THE TRUTH.
Rachel:
WELL, WHAT IS
THE TRUTH?
YEAH.
YEAH, WHAT'S
GOING ON?
I SLEPT WITH MONICA.
WELL, LET'S...
LET'S SEE WHAT EVERYBODY
THINKS OF THAT.
OH, NO.
YOU SLEPT WITH MY SISTER?
UH, YES...
BUT IT WAS...
WE JUST DID IT ONCE...
IN LONDON.
THIS IS NOT GOOD
FOR MY RAGE.
MONICA, IS THIS TRUE?
OF COURSE IT'S TRUE.
HOW ELSE WOULD YOU EXPLAIN
ALL THE WEIRD STUFF
THAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
YES, IT'S TRUE.
Rachel:
IF IT ONLY HAPPENED
THAT ONE TIME,
HOW COME WE FOUND
YOUR UNDERWEAR IN OUR APARTMENT
THE OTHER DAY?
UH... OY.
THAT WAS THE UNDERWEAR
I WAS WEARING
THAT NIGHT IN LONDON.
RIGHT, MONICA?
I GUESS I WANTED TO KEEP IT...
AS A SOUVENIR.
MY GOD, MONICA.
ARE YOU SURE, JOE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
JUST A SEX ADDICT?
NO, AND IF ANYONE'S
A SEX ADDICT HERE,
IT'S MONICA.
YEAH, YEAH.
SHE HAS BEEN TRYING TO GET ME
BACK IN THE SACK
EVER SINCE LONDON.
SO THAT'S WHY
SHE GAVE YOU
A NAKED PICTURE
OF HERSELF.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
AND THE VIDEO CAMERA?
UH, MONICA?
I GUESS I SET UP
THE VIDEO CAMERA
TO TRY AND ENTICE JOEY.
BUT, SADLY,
I COULD NOT
BE ENTICED.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, YOU REALLY KEPT
JOEY'S UNDERWEAR?
WHY?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I'M MONICA.
I'M DISGUSTING.
I STALK GUYS AND KEEP
THEIR UNDERPANTS.
WELL, I THINK
WE'VE ALL LEARNED SOMETHING
ABOUT WHO'S DISGUSTING
AND WHO'S NOT.
HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO GET BACK
TO MY BUCKET.
I'M ONLY EATING THE SKIN
SO THE CHICKEN'S UP FOR GRABS.
YOU WERE MAKING
A GOOD POINT
UNTIL YOU
GOT CUT OFF.
I KNOW. WHAT'S UP
WITH THAT GIRL MONICA?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T COME
WITH HER.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY, GUESS WHAT?
I JUST CONVINCED CARL
TO GIVE US A TEST NEXT WEEK.
A TEST?!
OH, COME ON, TESTS
MAKE US ALL BETTER LEARNERS.
OH, YEAH! WE SHOULD
HAVE ESSAY QUESTIONS!
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]